no but not that betrayal and also I have to
no pero esa traición no y además tengo
tell you that tomorrow morning it's a
deciros que mañana por la mañana es un
fake live show I don't mind
falso directo a mí no me importa
admitting it but tomorrow there's a live show
reconocerlo pero mañana hay un directo
on the main channel and I'm going to give it today the
en el canal principal y voy a dar hoy el
guest is a very famous person in the
invitado es una persona muy famosa del
world of gossip okay the other day
mundo del corazón vale el otro día
we had Lidia Loano and tomorrow we have
tuvimos a Lidia loano y mañana tenemos a
another one the thing is that I also have
otro lo que pasa es que también tengo
a video on the main channel tomorrow and
mañana en el canal principal un vídeo y
a live show with Trium So since
un directo con trium Entonces como el
I have lunch on Sunday I don't know if I should
domingo tengo una comida no sé si el
put the fake live show with the guest
falso directo con el invitado ponerlo
for Sunday Look what I'm telling you, I mean
para el domingo Fíjate lo que te digo o
today I'm going to announce the name today I'm
sea hoy lo voy a anunciar el nombre hoy
going to say the name yes or yes Ah okay I
el nombre lo voy a decir sí o sí Ah vale
had to have set the goal the
tenía que haber puesto entonces la meta
objective It should have been
la el objetivo Tendría que haber sido
for that no Of course it's wrong there's an
para eso no Claro est mal hay un
objective if the objective is met and
objetivo si se cumple el objetivo y
we're halfway through the live show or
estamos por la mitad del directo o lo
whatever Well I say it I say the name of the
que sea Pues lo digo digo el nombre del
guest that I think
del invitado que yo creo que va a
people are going to like a lot I'm going to do it I'm
gustarle mucho a la gente lo voy a lo
going to do it again on the main channel
voy a hacer otra vez en el principal
because I think I should take those interviews
porque creo que esas entrevistas debería
there I don't know if I'm
llevarla para allá no sé si me estoy
wrong or not eh And then Here I upload
equivocando o no eh Y luego Aquí subo
click and so on But  Today I'm going to tell you the
click y demás Pero hoy os voy a decir el
name and I think you're going to like it, not
nombre y creo que os va a gustar no lo
even they know it, eh, I mean, I think you're going to
saben ni ellos eh o sea creo que os va a
like it a lot, we know, let's see, let's see,
gustar mucho sabemos a ver a ver la la
people are really looking forward to
gente tiene muchas ganas
bringing that character, let's see, let's
de de de que trajera ese personaje a ver
see, yeah, yeah So, it's from the universe
a ver sí sí Enton pues es del universo
that we deal with, that's what the univ has
que nosotros tratamos eso es Lo univ
repeated, but there have already been. Ah, there have
repetido pero ya ha estado Ah
n't been people from her environment. Of
no ha estado gente de su entorno Ya
course, there have been people from her environment, there have been
claro ha habido gente de su entorno ha
many people from her environment, in
habido mucha gente de su entorno de
fact. Of course, but someone has been there who
hecho Claro pero ha estado alguien que
is, let's say, from her family, almost. Well, well, well, with us, of
es vamos de su familia casi bueno bueno
course, let's shut up. Don't
bueno cnos claro vamos a callarnos No me
tell me Matamoros is coming. I'm not going to
digas que viene Matamoros no te lo voy a
tell you now. I'm not going to tell you, I'm going to
decir ahora no te lo voy a decir te lo
tell you when when
voy a decir cuando cuando cuando
we get to the Super chat, but
lleguemos a los Super chat pero
well, of course, from the universe, from the universe, it's
bueno claro del universo del universo es
okay, but it's powerful, it's powerful, of course, it
vale pero es potente es potente claro
's people and Marta Riesco. Let's see, Marta
estáa gente y Marta riesco a ver Marta
Riesco is powerful too, but Marta
riesco es potente también pero Marta
Riesco has already come. Here is her house,
riesco ha venido ya aquí está su casa
practically, you know, I mean, she comes a lot.
prácticamente sabes o sea viene mucho a
I would like to start with something light
mí me gustaría empezar con algo flojito
and then we'll raise the level,
y ya luego vamos a ir subiendo el nivel
raising the level, okay. And then  Yesterday I
subiendo el nivel vale Y entonces Ayer
found myself uh I was starting the
me encontré eh estaba yo en empezando la
salsería apparently this was happening
salsería por lo visto esto ocurría
while I was with Marina on
mientras que yo estaba con Marina en
and here on the
e aquí en el programa de de de los
Wednesday program and suddenly I found myself with
miércoles y de repente me encontré con
this okay I reacted and I was a
con esto vale yo reaccioné y me quedé un
little bit caught or rather the truth is that it scares me a
poco ya pillado o sea la verdad es que
little bit I don't know how to
me da un poco de miedo no sé cómo
react to this I don't know if you have
reaccionar a esto no sé si lo habréis
commented on it on your channels yoy no yoy
comentado en vuestro canales yoy no yoy
no
no
commented listen now now now Loren now
comentado escuch ahora ahora ahora Loren
good good
ahora buenas buenas
night I just wanted to say are you
noches Solamente quería decir Me
listening to me you're not listening to me we hear you we
escucháis no me estáis escuchando te
hear you look I wanted to tell
oímos te oímos mira quería decirle al
Mr. Harvey Oliveira that I have never
Señor Harvey oliveira que yo jamás
entered that man's Channel he never has
entrado en el Canal de ese señor nunca
any I'm just going to tell him
yene ninguno Solamente le voy a decir
one thing the next
una cosa la próxima
time I come back is to take out this space and to
vez que vuelva é sacar este espacio y a
get everyone angry I'm going to send him a
ponernos verdes a todas le voy a dar un
little message so that he can put it up tomorrow
recadito para que se lo mañana lo ponga
if he wants Fabio Oliveira do you know Mr.
si quiere Fabio oliveira conoces a Don
Rafael Carrión Moreno from Seville the
Rafael Carrión Moreno de Sevilla el
president
presidente
of Real Sevilla do you know who he is
de del Real del Sevilla sabes quién es
No I work there and there are five lawyers
No yo trabajo ahí í hay cinco abogados
I've been in their house with them since I was very
Yo estoy en su casa con ellos desde muy
little finishing their  Children listen to me one
pequeña acando a sus hijos escúchame una
thing, dude, they know you about your life, from p
cosa quillo te conocen s tu vida de de p
to peace, from everything where you live. Everything listen to me,
a paz de todo donde vive Todo escúchame
the least you can do is put this
en la mínima que vuelvas a poner este
space back on Pilar, Marimar, Maria,
espacio a Pilar a Marimar a María a
Juana, Lola, all of us who are
Juana a Lola a todas las que estamos
here to get green, listen to me, the
aquí a ponernos verdes escúchame la
patio is going for you. Not me, but my bosses are going there, they
patio Va por ti Yo no pero van ahí mis
have a lot of money and they are
jefes que tienen mucha pasta y que son
very rich people from Seville, they are going to go after
gente muy ricas de Sevilla van a ir a
you because I have already warned them, you
por ti porque ya los tengo avisados
know, and whatever I say, they are going to do
sabes y lo que yo diga hagan van a hacer
because they love me madly Because I have been
porque me quieren con locura Porque
with them for many years, are you
llevo muchos años con ellos estás
listening because my husband is from
escuchando porque mi marido es de
Seville, I am from Extremadura, but my children
Sevilla yo soy extremeña pero mis hijos
are Andalusian, just like you are, from
son andaluces igual que lo eres tú de
Seville, also from Alcalá del Río and from
Sevilla también de alcal del río y de
Gerena, are you listening to me? Well, you
gerena me estás escuchando bueno que
know that I know your life,
sepas que sé tu vida ya se lo he dicho
I have already told Rafael, who found out about your life and I already
yo a Rafael que averiguó tu vida y ya la
know it, I know who you are, where you live, I know who you are,
sé des a sé de quién eres dónde vives sé
cana that comes and I know everything. Now
eres c aña que viene y sé todo ahora
tomorrow you put it out there and that, they are going to come after
mañana lo pones y lo eso que van a ir a
you, eh, be very careful, eh, you don't
por ti eh ten mucho cuidado eh que tú no
know who you are with.  you're getting involved now
sabes con quién te estás metiendo ahora
eh you're not getting involved with any random
eh que no te estás metiendo con ninguna
person or any choni or
cualquiera ni con ninguna choni ni con
any lowlife No I'm not any
ninguna barre bajera No yo no soy nada
of that son I'm very educated and I'm
de eso hijo Yo soy muy educada y estoy
with people of great prestige and
con gente de mucho prestigio y de mucha
education Well I can only say one thing
educa Bueno solo puedo decir una cosa
here because the first thing I want to say
aquí por yo lo primero que quiero decir
now is to each and every one of you to give your
ahora os deo a cada uno que de vuestra
opinion eh eh A hug to the family of the
opinión eh eh Un abrazo a la familia del
president of Sevilla Don Carrión okay he
presidente del Sevilla Don Carrión vale
passed away about a year and a half
que falleció hace un año y medio
ago Okay and I'm sorry that this
aproximadamente Vale y lamento que esta
lady is using his name to make this
señora utilice su nombre para hacer esta
barbaric threat from here on out and that
barbaridad de amenaza a partir de aquí y
's what I was going to tell you that I'm very scared I would
es lo que te iba a decir que mucho miedo
be scared because I'm scared of the
Yo sí que tendría miedo porque yo a los
dead and I'm scared because jolly
muertos y eso tengo miedo porque jolly
is something that is unknown and the threat
es algo que no se conoce y la amenaza te
comes from a dead person more or less I don't know
viene de un muerto más o menos no lo sé
with Laija or with who would get in
con laija o con que se pondría en
touch with him but she hasn't told
contacto con él pero no se lo ha dicho
the gentleman but the Lord is dead and he
al señor pero el Señor está muerto y le
told him to watch you from
ha dicho que que te vigile desde más
beyond or whatever let's see she asked her
allá o có a ver ella la ha preguntado
about me and the man knew me man if he
por mí y el hombre me conocía hombre si
's in another dimension of course maybe
está en otra dimensión claro a lo mejor
the man has powers to  see everything and
el hombre tiene poderes para ver todo y
know everything it could be if you're careful this
saber todo puede ser si te cuidado esta
car doesn't show you a
coche no te aparezca una cabeza de
horse's head in your bed or something tomorrow
caballo en la cama o algo mañana
when that's because in the afterlife there is no
cuando eso eso es que en el más allá no
data protection law Javi
hay ley de protección de datos Javi
of course that's why she dares to do anything
claro por eso se atreve a cualquier cosa
eh besides if you dare I mean trust yourself
eh además si te atreves O sea fíate tú
the lady so polite no And not at all
la señora tan educada no Y para nada
barri bajera or anything like that eh No no no no no
barri bajera ni nada de eso eh No no no
no with prestigious people eh
no no no con gente de prestigio eh en
like mafia eh I know where Javi lives be
plan mafiosa eh sé dónde vive Javi
careful that when she goes out she goes to take out
cuidado que cuando salga salga a sacar
the trash but she says that there are five
la basura pero dice que hay cinco
lawyers in the house but the man is no longer there won't
abogados en la casa pero el hombre ya no
be four because the man is
está no habrá cuatro ya porque el hombre
missing no or what Yes but apart from that I know I mean no matter how
falta no o qué Sí pero aparte yo que sé
much money you have you
o sea por mucho dinero que tú tengas tú
have a lawyer you don't have five no
tienes un abogado no tienes cinco no a
unless you have a work one other
no ser que tengas uno laboral otro
the
el
danger they do whatever she wants
peligro hacen lo que ella quiera que
she scrubs very well and she can't
ella frega muy bien y no se la puede
miss it no no no But because they love her
perder no no no Pero porque la quieren
so much it's that I love her because the typical
mucho es que me encanta porque la típica
lady who feels loved no I know she
señora que se siente querida no que se
wants to act like everyone loves me
que se las quiere dar de a mí me quiere
and and what and what she says You
todo el mundo y y que tal y que dice Tú
know who this is the president of
sabes quién es este el presidente del
Sevilla  Football Club okay asks him about
Sevilla fúbol Club vale le pregunta por
you and knows you of course I'm going to be
ti y te conoce claro yo voy deir
clear and without meaning to offend
clamente y sin ánimo de de ofender a
anyone but of course I'm not a brother-in-law about football, not
nadie pero claro yo de fútbol cuñado no
completely ignorant, I didn't know anything.
ignorante completamente yo no sabía nada
Last night when I saw the click in the
Yo anoche cuando vi el click en la
salsería I wasn't surprised because true
salsería a mí no me extrañó porque verad
you knew in Seville by luck or
tú conocido en Sevilla por por suerte o
by misfortune Well yes, I was a
por desgracia Pues sí que sido un
little bit no when I was a kid a little bit of a
poquito no cuando chaval un poquito
scoundrel and then whether you like it or not yes, they
cafre y entonces quieras que no sí que
knew about me but of course Eh well that didn't
se sabía de mí pero claro Eh pues no me
surprise me of course what I didn't know was
ha extrañado eso claro lo que yo no
that the man was dead is that
sabía que el hombre estaba muerto es que
very strong very strong I haven't
muy fuerte muy fuerte Yo esto no lo he
seen this and also the question of this is
visto y además la la cuestión de esto es
the warning not threat that there is on the
la advertencia no amenaza que hay por
part of this lady for taking up a
parte de esta señora por sacar un
space that I don't know what's wrong with people
espacio que no sé qué le pasa a la gente
with the space that they think is
con el espacio que se creen que son
private Well look before
privados Pues mira pues antes de
warning instead of making a space you
advertir en vez de hacer un espacio te
go with you go Skype with your friends and
vas con te vas Skype con tu amigas y
chat and there it remains private
charl y ahí si qued da en privado
not with the issue of the space that she thinks
no con el tema del espacio que se cree
is something is she says that they are anonymous But
que es algo es dice que son anónima Pero
you are doing something
tú estás haciendo una cosa
public of course we are anonymous we are
pública claro somos anónimas somos
anonymous
anónimas
the lady to me  continue eh I have to say
la señora me sigue eh tengo que decir
that she follows me on Twitter that I
que me sigue en Twitter que lo la he
looked her up to see who it was no and the
buscado para ver quién era no y la
lady follows me on Twitter and all her
señora me sigue en Twitter y todos sus
Twitter feeds are photos with hearts of
Twitter son fotos con corazones de
Antonio David photos with hearts
Antonio David fotos con corazones
Antonio but everything eh everything everything love
Antonio pero todo eh todo todo amor
Antonio David I mean as if it were her her
Antonio David o sea como si fuera su su
Justin Bieber not the typical No sir like that I am
Justin Bieber no la típica No señor así
worried about people and I'm going to say that I am
a mí me preocupa gente y va decir que a
worried about people from where
mí me preocupa gente de dónde
precisely Where she comes from that she has
precisamente De dónde viene que tiene
these behaviors a bit similar
estos comportamientos un poco parecido
similar to people we already know not
similares a gente que ya conocemos no
that we have eaten clist the way she
que hemos comado clista la forma de
speaks is totally classist eh And that she
hablar es un totalmente clasista eh Y
wants to distinguish herself with pasta and all that that is
que se quiere distingir de pasta y todo
classism she wants to be
eso eso es de clasismo se quiere hacer
distinguished and then really by how she
distinguir y luego realmente por cómo se
expresses herself and by how I mean she is someone else
expresa y por cómo o sea es alguien más
and she is trying to make it seem that of course
y está intentando hacer ver de que claro
exactly what she handles for her and
exactamente que que maneja para ella y
for all her companions you cannot we cannot
para todos sus compañeras no puedes no
name any of them anyone from the
podemos nombrar a ninguna a nadie del
space I mean okay for all the
espacio o sea vale para todas las
companions and for all but in that
compañeras y para todas pero en ese
space I think they stopped her
espacio cre que la pararon los pies
eh they stopped her feet it will be it will be now
eh le pararon los pies será será ahora
we are going to see more clips but it will be a little bit
vamos a ver más clip pero será un poco
of a stance of course it is a space that is
de postura claro es un espacio que se
dedicated let's go and in fact this is coming
dedica vamos y de hecho esto viene
because I don't do everything from time to time
porque yo de vez en cuando no todo
because it's three or four hours of space every day
porque son tres o cuat horas cada día de
and I eat to fill you know to
espacio y yo como para relleno tú sabes
laugh and such this is
para reírme no y tal est es la señora
this lady Pilar verun who has been on
esta Pilar verun que ha estado por
channels like Peppa's she's like very
canales como el de la Peppa es como muy
Also she speaks like very redich like
Además ella habla así como muy redich
very such as if she were very
así como muy tal como si fuera muy
polite but then the aunt doesn't stop
educada pero luego la tía no para de
missing
faltar
this is this is a space that is all
esto es esto es un space que es todo el
[ __ ] day insulting me you know and I
[__] día insultándome sabes y me
meet yesterday with this lady who says she has
encuentro aller con esta señora que dice
n't done anything to me you don't know who I
a mí no me ha hecho nada no sabes quién
am but I'm going to cut the
yo soy pero yo voy a cortar aquí el
crap here I'm going to split the cod here I
rollo yo voy a partir aquí el bacalao yo
'm the coolest that all of you aren't and it's
soy la más Guay que todos ustedes no y
like it's not that you do it
es como en que ya no es que lo hagas
because Look I think that all of us who
porque Mira yo creo que todos los que
are here who more and who less
estamos aquí quien más y quien menos
surely at some point and there are
seguro que en algún momento y de mí hay
many clicks from me no that they throw it
muchos clicks no que me lo echan mucho
in my face a lot no but it's moments in which
en cara no pero es momentos en los que
someone turns you on you are
alguien pues te calienta estás muchas
live for many hours and in the end it's
horas en directo y al final es la vida
real life it's like the one that doesn't Then you
real es como el que no Entonces te
fight with someone someone says
peleas con con alguien alguien te dice
something strong to you or says something to you about the family
algo fuerte o te dice algo de la familia
or makes you  I don't know what And you can jump at
o te hace no sé qué Y tú puedes saltar
a given moment and fail in the form And
un momento dado y fallar en la forma Y
such But of course she calmly thinks it's a
tal Pero claro ella tranquilamente le
good idea or that it looks good to do
parece buena idea o que queda bien hacer
this here like a
esto aquí a lo
Corleones is that it is She thought it was a
corleones es que es eso A ella le ha
joke, pleased Yes yes yes she
parecido una vacilada quedado gusto Sí
said said this this is over I'll stop it I'm
sí sí ha dicho dicho esto esto se acaba
here today quickly Here I'll
esto lo paro Yo hoy aquí rapidito Aquí
shut them up I'll shut them up
les callo yo la boca le callo yo la boca
quickly
rápido a
because they are all There is one who is a prosecutor or
porque todas son Hay una que es fiscal o
daughter of a prosecutor or mother they all have expensive ones she has it
hija de fiscal o madre todas tien caros
fried me the Mar has it fried they are
tiene frita a mí me tiene frita la Mar
not normal ladies they are ladies let
no son señoras normales son señoras
's go super well connected with
vamos super bien conectadas con
Prosecutors at most Yes yes what was
Fiscales todo lo más Sí sí que estaba
happening in the space so that these
pasando en el espacio para que esta
people get angry because it is commented or
gente se mosque porque se comente o se
seen no and they are not
vea no y no la
seen beyond the circle but they are
vean más allá del círculo pero están
always like that always when I heard them they
siempre así yo siempre que las escuchado
are always always insulting
alguna vez están sipre sipre insultando
always they are Like it's like
sipre siempre están Así es como un
poison right like an always but every
veneno verdad como un siempre pero todos
day in I don't know how many nicknames The
los días en no sé cuánto motes El Bueno
Good well they put everyone in a bad mood they are
bueno ponen verde a todo el mundo
always pissed off always I have not
siempre están cabreadas siempre yo no
seen them but always the clicks that I see
las he visto pero sieme los clis que veo
of them it comes to my head that  they are
de ellas me viene a la cabeza que están
in a cave and they are like the witches
en una cueva y están así como las brujas
of Salen all messing around And
de Salen todas liando alguna Y
preparing some
preparando alguna
pima V
pima V
mir they are Look I love the photos eh
mir están Mira Me encantan las fotos eh
Because one puts on a Pomeranian dog
Porque una se pone un perrete pomerania
the other puts on this one puts on it's that this one is
la otra se pone esta se pone es que esta
messing with Marta Riesco she
se mete con Marta riesco le falta
disrespects to Kisi and has like a filter
respeto a to kisi y tiene como un filtro
on top a filter on top a
en lo alto un filtro en lo alto un
filter on top a filter looks like a
filtro en lo alto un filtro parece una
photo made with Artificial Intelligence
foto hecha con Inteligencia artificial a
based on a photo of hers already taken Of course
raíz de una foto suya ya ya hecha Claro
but it's like when you put a you haven't
pero es como cuando tú pones un tú no
made a can Face app the one to put a
has hecho un can Face app la de poner un
filter to make yourself older for
filtro para ponerte más viejo por
example no filter filter filter your face can already be seen
ejemplo no filtro filtro filtro ya se ve
like Deti the only pretty one is
la cara como deti la única bonita es la
Elsa's which is the very typical Pomeranian dog
Elsa que es el perro de pomerania muy
let's listen to another piece the
típico vamos a escuchar otro trozo la
next time he comes back to take out this
próxima vez que vuelva él a sacar este
space and to make us all green I'm
espacio y a ponernos verdes a todas le
going to give him unito so that tomorrow he puts it
voy a dar unito para que mañana lo ponga
if Oliva do you know Don Rafael Carón
si oliva conoces a Don Rafael carón
Moreno from Seville the president of Real
Moreno de Sevilla el presidente real
Seville do you know who he is No I work
Sevilla sabes quién es No yo trabajo ahí
there there are five lawyers I am in his house with
ahí hay cin abogados estoy su casa con
it makes it very small when his children
ello hace muy pequeña cuando a sus hijos
listen to me one thing you  They know your life of
escuchame una cosa te conocen tu vida a
everything where you live everything scales at the
de todo dond vive todo escame en la
least that you put this space back
mínima que vuelvas a poner este espacio
to Pilar to Marimar to Maria to Juana to Lola
a Pilar a Marimar a María a Juana a Lola
to all of us who are here to put us
a todos los que estamos aquí a ponos
green listen to me the go for I don't but they are going that
verd escúchame la va por Yo no pero van
has a lot of gaza that they are they go because I
que tiene mucha gaza que son van porque
have warned you know and what I said they are going to
tengo avisado sabes y lo que yo di van
do because you with madness Because I have been
hacer porque ti con locura Porque llevo
with them for many years you are
muchos años con ellos está
listening son you of chair also of the river
escuchando hij tú de silla tambi del rí
deena you are listening well that you know
deena estás escuchando bueno que sepas
that your life I have already told you to Rael that
que tu vida ya se lo dicho yo a rael que
your life is of p to Pas Whose are you
tu vida s de p a Pa s De quién eres
where you live s who the cña that comes and s
dónde vive s qui la cña que viene y s
everything now tomorrow puts it And that they are going for
todo ahora mañana lo pone Y eso van por
you Be very careful knowing now they
ti Mucho cuidado sabendo ahora no te
are not lying to you with any just anyone or
están miendo con ninguna cualquiera ni
with any chy or with any barera No
con ninguna chy ni con ninguna barera No
I am not like that I am very educated and I
yo no so de esoo Yo soy muy educada y
am with people of great prestige and
estoy con gente de mucho prestigio y de
education you know and I know many
mucha educación sabes y conco mucha
people high society because suos are
gente alta sociedad porque suos está
attending what you have never gone to
atendiendo lo que tú no has ido nunca a
box to place Well to fairs the best
palco a sitio Bueno a ferias lo mejor
place in April Who are you  I am
sitio de abril Quién eres tú yo s soy
a worker but I have a lot of
una trabajadora pero tengo mucho
prestige Because I work with people with
prestigio Porque trabajo con gente de
a lot of money and people with a lot of money who
mucho dinero y gente de muchaa que
can ruin your life if you come back I'll kick
pueden empapelar y tu vida como vuelvas
your [ __ ] out. He's
a seguir saco la [__] tuya me está
listening to me now.
escuchando ahora
Hitor calm down. No, no, well, threaten. No, no,
hitor calma No no bien amenazar no no
well, threaten. Loren. It's really not
bien amenazar Loren de verdad que no es
informative. There's still someone who
inform
offends you in any way. You have the
hay alún ya si te ofenden en algo Tienes
right to complain. I don't feel offended by this man. It's
t derecho a reclamar yo con este señor
true that we are the bad that
verad de que somos mal que
we are. He says what he
somos diga lo que
wants. Esc. When it comes down to it,
quiera esc a la hora de la verdad que
that man says scum, you are scum,
ese señor diga gentuza eres gentuza casi
it's almost a medal because that man has
es una medalla porque ese señor se ha
ruined his prestige on YouTube so long ago
cargado su prestigio en YouTube hace
that it's not worth threatening him.
bueno que no vale la pena amenazarlo de
I'm not loving. I'm only
verdad yo no estoy amar solamente estoy
saying that if he puts things up
diciendo que como saque cosas puestas en
again, telling us things and threatening
otra vez diciéndonos cosas y amenazando
him that we are such and such, that we are which, what the
él que somos unas tales que somos unas
[ __ ] doesn't he know us, that he does
cuales qué [__] no conoce a nosotros que
n't know us, Lor, this eh. This
no conoce nosotros lor este eh Este
man is characterized by insulting, exactly,
señor se caracteriza por insultar exact
and listen to me Loren, from me he's not going to get
y escúchame Loren de mí no va a obtener
an insult, a threat, eh, or an
ni un insulto ni una amenaza eh ni una
insult, or slander. No, really.
injuria ni una calumnia No de verdad
Well, this one.  This is Pilar
Bueno Esta que está hablando la Pilar
Vera speaking, who has a Twitter account
Vera que tiene la la cuenta de Twitter
dedicated to me, I mean it's completely
dedicada a mí o sea es completamente
dedicated to me and she talks to people
dedicada a mí y se va hablando con gente
because she and I know that there are people
porque ella e Yo sé que es que hay gente
of all colors and from all
de todos los colores y de todos los
teams, no, but normally you follow
equipos no pero normalmente tú sigues a
people who have your ideas, that you
gente que que tienen tus ideas que te
like the way they talk, that you agree with, no,
gusta como habla que estás de acuerdo no
but this lady spends her whole account being
pero esta señora va toda su cuenta como
very, very, very boxing, very right-wing, I
muy muy muy de muy de box muy de derecha
don't know, I don't know how much, criticizing Irene
no sé no sé cuánto criticando Irene
Montero, I don't know how much, but then she follows
Montero no sé cuánto pero luego sigue a
everyone who throws [ __ ] at me. Eh, whether it's as
a a todo el que me tire [__] Eh ya sea
Podemos-like as possible, I mean it's somewhat
lo más podemita posible o sea es algo
incoherent, I mean it seems like it's not. I mean, what I mean
incoherente o sea parezca que no O sea
is that her
lo que quiero decir es que se basa su
account is based on her criteria, it's Javi Oliveira, yes or
cuenta su criterio es Javi oliveira sí o
no, yes, that above politics, of
no sí que por encima de política de lo
whatever, hatred for you is above
que sea el odio a ti está por encima de
any exactly, and she says, I won't
de cualquier exactamente y dice yo no lo
slander you and I say, but yes, I have a
calum y digo pero si yo tengo aquí una
folder here of things that she has told me and she
carpeta de cosas que ella me ha dicho y
started to tell me that I asked to
se puso a decirme que yo pedí para
defend her friend Peppa because she is a
defender a su amiga Peppa porque esta es
friend of Peppa from the 240 and she
amiga de la Peppa la de los 240 y se
started, if I don't remember, I think  that they
puso si no me si no recuerdo creo que
ended they ended badly right because
terminaron terminaron mal verdad pues
to defend her from the 240 she started
para defenderla de los 240 esta se puso
saying of course I would take it from one of these
a decir claro lo cogería de alguno de
youtubers of the kids in
los youtubers estos de la chavalería a
half because on top of that she finds out half and she
media porque encima se entera a media y
started saying that I asked for money for
se puso a decir que yo pedí dinero para
donations so that people would donate
para donaciones para que la gente donara
to buy toys for children in a
para comprar juguetes para niños de un
hospital for children with cancer
hospital para niños de cáncer con cáncer
and that I should keep money that I am very fond of what belongs to
y que me queder dinero que soy muy amigo
others she put me the lady Here
de lo ajeno me puso la la señora Aquí
educated the one who does not slander you know we do not
educada la que no calumnia sabes
say we insult we are not like them and they
no dic insultamos no somos como ellos y
have the marim bad there this is that is that
tienen ahí a la marim mal esta que es
of insulting eh it is that it is
que eso es un eso de insultar eh es que
a come on that woman It is that from the
es un vamos esa mujer Es que desde que
beginning until the end she is all the time
empieza hasta que acaba es todo el rato
insulting she says we are not going to be like them
insultando dice no vamos a ser como
we here do not insult no
ellos nosotros aquí no insultamos no
but come on when she opens her mouth she starts and it is
pero vamos cu abre la boca empieza y es
a machine gun insulting that Marimar
una metralleta insultando esa la Marimar
comes from the front and you listen to her but it is that
viene de frente y la escuchas pero es
Patiño is With what thing with
que la Patiño esta Con qué cosa con
saying I
decir
say box of those of the football and everything with
digo palco de los del fútbol y todo con
her bosses with her bosses but the funny thing
sus jefes con sus jefes pero lo gracioso
is that she says it is not right to threaten when she has
es que dice no está bien amenazar cuando
already let her say everything  what she
ya la ha dejado decir todo lo que le ha
wanted to see from the beginning you can see her coming cut it out well no
la estás viendo venir córtala pues no
when she's already making her speech she says
cuando ella ya hace su speech dice
man I don't see it well eh It's not well
hombre no lo veo bien eh No está bien
beloved the woman told you that
amado la mujer te ha contado hasta que
she was from Extremadura and I don't know what that
ella era extremeña y que no sé qué que
I don't know the story what that's about but she
yo no s al cuento de qué viene eso pero
told you my husband is from Seville be
contado mi marido es de Sevilla
careful he
cuidadito
has to tell his life story be careful because she
tiene contar su vida un cuidadito que
is a friend of the Duchess of Alba
está es amiga de la Duquesa de Alba
because come on, what I don't know is how
porque vamos yo lo que no sé es cómo
this woman is still working in the
está trabajando todavía esta mujer en la
house of the and to the box Eh Well if she doesn't
casa de los y a palco Eh Pues como no me
throw a bottle at me from the box this is how it is
tire un un botel ía desde el palco así
no like it is from the park it
está no así como que está des el parco
has never happened to us when I was a kid who
nos ha pasado nunca cuando chaval que a
maybe played ball down there and they
lo mejor jugaba ahí la pelota abajo y te
threw bleach at you the neighbors milk tian
echaban lejías las vecinas leche tian
water they threw
agua tiraban
bleach watch the boxes when you go around
lejía vigila los palcos cuando vayas por
there watch the boxes don't let
ahí vigila los palcos no vaya a estar
her be around there listen to me she has made me
ella por ahí escúchame a m me ha hecho
very G she says You talk to her and you
mucha G que dice Tú hablas con ella y tú
talk to her and she tells you that she
hablas con ella y esta te dice que ha
had coffee with the Duchess of Alba
tomado café con la Duquesa de Alba la
last week Well if it's like the one that they have
pasada Bueno si ca como el de que tienen
a lot of money that their friends have a lot of
mucho dinero que sus amigos tienen mucho
money and they put paper on me Well
dinero y me ponen empapelado Pues
as long as they put paper on me in billet I'm
mientras que me empapel en billet yo
happy you
encantado
know he's here asking for a
sabes está aquí pidiendo
member It's that I also imagine him
miembro Es que además me lo imagino
saying dude please eh let's go with
diciendo quillo por favor eh vamos con
Javi let's go against Javi I mean asking a
Javi vamos contra Javi o sea pidiéndole
favor to a a to another person this group of
favor a a a a otra persona este grupo de
lawyers to go against you when there is
abogados para ir contra ti cuando no hay
nothing nor they have anything nor Simply
nada ni ni tienen nada ni Simplemente
because you have commented something about these
porque hayas comentado algo de de esta
people no but it makes a lot of sense eh I mean
gente no pero tiene mucho sentido eh o
you imagine It's like the
sea tú imagínate Es como que los
lawyers can paper you because there are
abogados te pueden empapelar porque son
five of them it's like the five of them were
cinco es como si los cinco fueran más
stronger not because between five against one and it
fuerte no porque ent cinco contra uno y
's like but I'm going to tell your whole life
es como pero voy a contar toda tu vida
too also but it's that same
también también pero es que esa misma
threat knows everything about you knows everything
amenaza lo sabe todo de ti lo sabe todo
about
de
you new position You know to go and
ti cargo nuevo Ya sabes para [__] y
notify the family of that man to
avisar a la familia de ese señor que le
report him the family you don't even need to
denuncien la familia ya no necesitas ni
get involved because you are the one who are going to
meterte tú porque tú a quién vas a
report a dead person it's not the family
denunciar a un muerto no es la familia
who has to report him I
quien la tiene que denunciar
didn't count on the family and saying that
no contao con la familia y decirlo
dead person knows everything about
muerto sabe todo de
you is crazy  maybe she doesn't know He has
ti es de locos a lo mejor no sabe Ha
passed away that's realistic every
fallecido eso realista todo
guy's idea that the man has passed away
tío idea de que el hombre Ha fallecido
she's not that it gives the impression that
ella no es que da la impresión esa de
she doesn't know that he has died I
que ella no sabe que se ha muerto yo
think that she doesn't know it either I think that she doesn't
creo que tampoco lo sabe yo creo que
know it either I understand I understand that
tampoco lo sabe Entiendo entiendo que
when you mention her because you don't know that he
cuando la mencionas porque no sabes que
has died or that he has another
se ha muerto a no s que tenga otro
relative who has the same name but of course
familiar que se llama igual pero claro
the president of Sevilla
ha dicho el presidente del Sevilla
Fútbol Club of Real Sevilla said, Real
Fútbol Club del Real Sevilla el real
Sevilla of course
Sevilla claro
And what do you think that I considered in a
la Y qué pensáis de que consider en una
lake to call him rabble I think that tomorrow
lago llamarle gentuza yo creo que mañana
they can start the space with a
pueden empezar el espacio con una
badge that says rabble not
chapita que ponga gentuza no
as they like they can't
como gusta no pueden
consider themselves then the thugs are us
considerarse luego los macarras somos
from here you know those who follow this
los de aquí sabes los que siguen este
channel Ah but we take it with great honor
canal Ah pero lo llevamos a mucha honra
Eh well let's see but well of course I don't know the
Eh bueno a ver pero bueno claro no s el
concept of thug when there's a
concepto de macarra cuando hay una
ladies there every night Go on and
señoras ahí todas las noches Dale que te
talk it's like an exercise I mean
pego al palique es como un ejercicio o
I leave them because it's like a relief
sea yo las dejo porque es como un desago
But I simply comment noas you
Pero simplemente yo comento noas te
come out totally no but how good like
salen totalmente no pero cu buenas como
the movie no not mentioned then yeah
la película no no mencionado entonces sa
let's listen The
vamos a escuchar El
last Wait that still that still
último Espérate que todavía que todavía
the mobster is me eh  there I am with me
el mafioso soy yo eh ahí estoy con mi
with one of my employees okay ha I'm
con uno de mis empleados vale ha estoy
with one of my employees the Indian well
con uno de mis empleados el indio bueno
that you already know that all these
que ustedes ya sabéis que todas las
accounts of El Indio Joy Hunter who
cuentas estas de El Indio Joy Hunter que
manipulates statistics and doesn't put the
manipula estadísticas y no pone el
first who he has to put it is not
primero a quien tiene que poner no son
all because they work for me And everything
todos porque trabajan para mí Y todo lo
that happens I'm machinating okay I
que pasa lo lo voy maquineo yo vale Yo
organize Hey Consuelo eh Do a
organizo Oye Consuelo eh Hazle un
live stream for this Carmen Do a live stream for
directo a este Carmen Hazle un directo a
this you know
este sabes
Tomorrow I'm going to think about it tomorrow it's
Mañana me lo voy a pensar mañana es
clear it's that tomorrow I would like it to
vi claro es que mañana me gustaría que
be a little more special Because it's
fuera un poco más especial Porque es
Friday Well here you have one of my
viernes Bueno aquí tenéis a uno de mis
employees not the one I hit not to
empleados no al que yo atizo no a que
do especially photo montages eh
haga sobre todo montaje fotográfico eh
above all I send this one a lot of
sobre todo a este le mando muchos
photo montages and here you have a
montajes fotográficos y aquí tenéis una
photo of me with him before I got my
foto mía con él antes de yo ponerme
hair done let's see they are Mor horalia of
pelo vamos a ver son Mor horalia de
balls I mean these how are
[__] o sea estos como están Yo es que
they I swear that I wouldn't have the life
os lo juro que a mí no me daría la vida
to be in charge of everything but as
para estar pendiente de todo pero como
Elsa said very well these people
muy bien Dice ha dicho Elsa esta gente
keep what with what they give what they
se queda con lo que con lo que da lo que
give cache that of that oh if not if this urge Well yes already already  I
da cache lo de que ay si no si esta gusa
had to get
Pues sí ya ya ya tenía que sacar a
Antonio Daviz out but let's see let's
Antonio daviz pero vamos a ver vamos a
see some riffraff if Tania doesn't
ver morrallas si no le saca Tania no le
get him out we won't get him out nobody will get him out
sacamos nosotros no le saca nadie estáis
you are here but if you are the riffraff for
vosotros pero si estáis la morraya para
whether Antonio David speaks or not speaks talk
si habla o no habla Antonio David hablar
about him and you don't say that Antonio David is not
de él y no decís que Antonio David no es
a God well we can
un Dios pues de Antonio David se puede
talk about Antonio David Look I am Antonio David I don't
hablar Mira yo soy antonio David que no
know that he's not going to do it he's not going to do it
sé que no lo va a hacer no lo va a hacer
because he's not used to doing it
porque no está acostumbrado a hacerlo
because then he would have to do
porque entonces tendría que hacer
live shows every day like
directos todos los días como el mafioso
your mobster and your giggles you know decona
vuestro y las risitas tuyas sabes decona
So when he does live shows he
Entonces él cuando hace directos queos
talks to you about
habla de
information talk about riffraff you know
información hablar de de gentucca sabes
how I call you Indian But you know the
cómo te digo indio Pero sabes lo
funny thing eh that you eh deny eh about
gracioso eh que vosotros eh renega eh de
this man he denys a movement rena
este hombre renega de un movimiento rená
of all the people then look you know
de de toda la gente entonces mira sabes
what what I tell you Indian India or
lo que lo que te digo indio India o
vice versa eh that between you you are
viceversa eh que de que entre vosotros
not going to you are not going to eat true
no os vais a no os vais a comer verdad
no no you don't have eh That this thing of we
no no no tenéis eh Esa esa cosa de le
are going to talk to him no because of course the
vamos a hablar no porque claro el
mobster is sacred because I How many
mafioso es sagrado porque yo Cuántas
times have you  I was telling the truth on Twitter when
veces te decía verdad por Twitter cuando
no we weren't blocked Well I didn't
no no estábamos bloqueados Bueno no te
block you, don't block me, what I was telling you is
bloqueé no me bloqueas que te decía por
why don't you talk about this thing about the mobster And
qué no hablas de esto de del mafioso Y
you stay quiet like the [ __ ] truth, you ca
tú calladito como una [__] verdad al
n't touch the mobster because you're the
mafioso no se le toca porque eres
mobster's employee, right? So,
trabajador del mafioso verdad Entonces
I'm Antonio David and I'm telling you the
eh yo yo soy antonio David y te lo digo
truth, Indian from Sindona and all the other
de verdad indio de sindona y a toda a
rabble, I'm Antonio David and I
toda la morraya yo soy antonio David y
support Tania
doy mi apoyo a Tania al
100% 100% I tell you, clo Because look,
100% al 100% te quo clo Porque mira
you guys are [ __ ] [ __ ], it's been
vosotros sois una [__] [__] ha sido
clear you don't defend anything, you
claro vosotros no defendis nada nunca
've never defended anything, eh, you've been
habéis defendido nada eh habéis sido
profiteers, you've been
unos aprovechados habéis sido unos
mercenaries of a
mercenarios de un
mobster who's a little bit, eh As soon as you
mafioso que ha un cachito eh En cuanto
saw the information wasn't
ya la información ya veíais que no venía
good, you went and I kept going, eh, like you're
bien ya fuisteis y seguí yendo eh Como
full of Antonio David and everything
llenas al cuello de Antonio David y todo
that surrounds Antonio David, it
lo que rodea a Antonio David no
's not just Antonio David, everything that
solamente es Antonio David todo lo que
surrounds him, that is to say, collaborators,
le rodea es decir colaboradores
defenders, everything that surrounds Antonio
Defensores todo lo que rodea Antonio
David, you're like full So I am
David sois como llenos Entonces yo soy
Antonio David and since I didn't give
antonio David y como no me importé ya
a [ __ ] [ __ ] anymore I'll tell you clearly
una [__] [__] así de claro te lo digo
neighbor and all the rabble Well, I'm
vecinda y a toda la morralla Pues yo soy
Antonio I'm doing a live stream when I do a
antonio hago un directo cuando haga un
live stream they just sent me something that I
directo me acaban de mandar una cosa que
have to tell you now a Plus tweet
os tengo que decir ahora un Plus tweet
which is that you're not going to wait for it I say
que es que no os lo Vais a esperar diga
well I support Tania 100% because Tania
pues apoyo a Tania al 100% porque Tania
has nothing to do with this matter it's that
no tiene nada que ver en estee asunto es
she's not guilty of anything Because we
que ella no es culpable de nada Porque
would have to investigate your lives to
habría que investigar vuestras vidas a
see what it is that you have because of course a
ver qué es lo que tenéis porque claro un
very strange man cla I don't remember what it is that you
hombre muy raro cla no me acuerdo que es
're talking about of of something
que estáis hablando de de de de algo
shameful because what I say I
vergonzoso porque yo lo que digo yo
can think that you because of course
puedo pensar que vosotros porque claro
those who are in jail also
los que están en las cárceles También
have social networks I can think
tienen redes sociales yo puedo pensar
that you are in jail in a
que vosotros estáis en una cárcel en un
psychiatric hospital I ca
psiquiátrico
n't and besides
no puedo y aparte
directly if she is she is already free she has
directo si está está ya libre ha
served her sentence sea in jail there is no
cumplido condena mar en la cárcel no hay
internet Honey
internet Cariño
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Mine because of course bad to think to
Mío porque es que claro malos a pensar a
be bad-minded I can think
ser mal pensados yo puedo pensar
anything about these scum these
cualquier cosa de esta gentuza esta
scum that is dedicated to taking
gentuza que se dedica a sacar cosas
private things from  anonymous people Well I
privadas de personas anónimas Pues yo
can think anything about these
puedo pensar cualquier cosa de esta
people
gentuza
seriously these people can't be
en serio estas personas no pueden estar
right in the head I don't [ __ ] with them they can't
bien de la cabeza a mí no me jod que no
be right in the head damn it
pueden estar bien de la cabeza [__]
because it just doesn't occur to me eh
porque es que a mí no se me ocurre eh
As much as I worship a
Por mucho que yo tenga adoración a un a
supreme being I say to them Hey but
un ser supremo a mí yo le digo Oye pero
what are you doing that you're talking about an
qué estás haciendo que estás hablando de
anonymous person that there are minors involved
una persona anónima que hay menores de
But what the [ __ ] are you doing
por medio Pero qué [__] estás haciendo
No no no no they they you
No no no no ellos ellos
how good it's
ti qué bueno es una maravilla en
really wonderful and they want to prohibit me from
realidad y me quieren prohibir
commenting on it here from the council they're going after
comentarlo aquí desde la conselo van a
you eh Hey joking Carmen It seems very
por ti eh Oye broma Carmen Me parece muy
suspicious to me eh I put it so that
sospechoso eh lo pongo para que no se
the cholo can't be seen that I have it here behind
vea el cholo que lo tengo aquí detrás
the Cholo of course that house isn't yours I've realized it
del Cholo claro esa casa no es tuya me
myself eh I think there are
he dado cuenta yo ya eh yo creo que son
bars behind eh No no it's that he gets
rejas por detrás eh No no es que se
up very early of course That's what I said
levanta muy temprano claro Así decía yo
Of course but the other one qualifying no it doesn't
Claro pero la otra matizando no no me
seem to me that you're from prison I don't think they
parece que des desde la cárcel no creo
don't
que no
worship them he says but if you
tien adoran alos le dice pero si te
go into her profile and it's all
metes en el perfil de ella y es todo
hearts Antonio David and now he says
corazones Antonio David y ahora dice
Antonio David is dedicated to  the information
Antonio David se dedica a la información
and he doesn't talk about rabble
y no se dedica a hablar de chumma él por
why doesn't he get involved because he doesn't
qu no se va mete porque es que esto no
like this he doesn't like to talk about anyone of
le gusta no le gusta hablar de nadie
course you can't talk about Antonio
claro no se puede hablar de Antonio
David he has a YouTube channel but
David que tiene un canal de YouTube pero
about you and about the others he does have a
de ti de los demás sí que tiene canal de
YouTube channel No well I'll talk about myself
YouTube No pues de mí ya hablo yo
too about fasd first of all I'd like to say congratulations
también de fasd yo primero decir que en
Sorry congratulations on signing Indio
Perdona enorabuena por fichar al Indio
because the truth is that he's great no
porque la verdad es que es genial no
but I haven't signed him now damn I've been
pero no lo he fichado ahora [__] llevo
with him for three or four years I send him to
ya con él tres o cuat años le mando
do montages of
hacer montajes de
faces how people explode with the
carit como explota la gente con los
montages damn I wish the least he
montad [__] Ojalá a mí lo mínimo que me
did to me the most was that you know
lo máximo que me hiciera fuera eso sabes
or the least the least even if it was you know
o lo mínimo lo mínimo aunque fuera sabes
montages of the face the joke of
montaj itos de la cara el cachondeo del
Indio you know But I've had it from the
Indio sabes Pero yo lo tengo ya desde el
beginning seg and Jo Ah is there and and
principio seg y al Jo Ah está ahí y y al
Jo Well competition here to see who is the
Jo Bueno competición aquí a ver quién
prettiest tonight or how
viene más guapa esta noche o cómo la
things are good night I come I come to
cosa buenas noches Yo vengo yo vengo a
put order Because here it is supposed that I
poner orden Porque aquí se supone que a
have the people on Twitter on my payroll not
la gente de Twitter la tengo a sueldo yo
you the one who you the one who you don't  No
no tú la que te la que te no no
no, I say to Joe, look, Joe, you have to
no a Joe le digo yo mira Joe tienes que
lie and say that I've had these visits,
mentir y decir que estas visitas he
this m, this one, put it
tenido yo este m a este ponle
except the one who's silently behind the scenes,
menos la que está en silencio por detrás
putting here and there on Twitter and pulling
poniendo aquí y allí en Twitter y maneja
the strings and that's why they call me the spider, it's
los hilos y por eso me llaman la araña
me, be careful, I have to give you all a It
soy yo cuidado tengo que daros un a
turns out that they're
Resulta ser que me
sending me, I'm not going to reveal the source, okay, I'm not
mandan no voy a revelar la Fuente vale
going to reveal the source, psychiatric
no voy a revelar la fente psiquiátrico
in the
en el
psychiatric hospital, that one, that spider there, eh, listen to me, they've caught me, they've
psiquiátrico esa ese crilla ahí eh
caught me, they've caught me, I don't know, suspects of Carmen
han pillado Yo no sé sospechos de Carmen
and
y de
Aras, the most problematic ones, also,
aras las más problemáticas además
eh, they've sent me evidence, eh, in addition, they've sent me
eh que me han mandado pruebas eh además
evidence, screenshots, but not
me han mandado pruebas captura per no
evidence because they've leaked anything
pruebas porque me hayan filtrado nada
private to me or anything like that, which they're going to
privado ni nada por el estilo que ya van
start,
a empezar
but rather they are things that the ladies on their
sino que son cosas que las señora en sus
social networks have public and it turns
redes sociales las tien públicas y es
out that this lady,
que resulta que esta señora
Yes, she's not from Extremadura or Seville or
Sí no es de extremadura ni de Sevilla ni
anything like that, I'm not going to say where, but let's see, it
nada de eso no voy dec donde pero a ver
's very far, it's like
es muy lejos es como
approximately, I don't know, but very far, very
aproximadamente No lo sé pero muy lejos
far, Okay,
muy lejos
very foreign, very, very
Vale muy extranjera muy muy muy
foreign, like those who take the one
extranjera como los que cogen la la de
from Loli, okay
esto de Loli vale de Loli pero bueno sí
Loli but well yes yes it is close okay it is close to where she said where she said she lived she said the city of Extremadura Extremaduran she said she was from Extremadura she didn't say she was from Extremadura but that she lived in Seville well she is from Merida actually okay but she does
Mérida en realidad vale pero
n't work with this man, I mean she
e no trabaja con este hombre o sea
works uh in a hotel according to her own
trabaja Eh en un hotel según sus propias
social networks man she's not going to work with this man
redes sociales hombre con este no va a
because he's not here maybe he
trabajar porque no está a lo mejor
worked as a child as a child V sa she can't
trabajó de chiquilla de niña V sa no
work No well it's that she works in
puede trabajar No pues es que trabaja en
a hotel I mean she has a public
un hotel O sea ella tiene pública
job in this hotel tomorrow tomorrow
trabajo en en este hotel mañana mañana
because you're exposing data of an
ya porque estás exponiendo datos de una
anonymous person tomorrow
persona anónima mañana
nobody said the debate tomorrow is no longer I
ya no dijo nadie el debate mañana ya no
lied I said that I work with
es he mentido he dicho que trabajo con
a man who is dead no and I
un hombre que está muerto no y le he
told her also of course the debate tomorrow is she
contado además claro el debate mañana es
said that I work in a hotel she
ha dicho que trabajo en un hotel ha
said Sure of course you're exposing
dicho Claro claro estás exponiendo toda
her whole life Everything everything Of course if for her it is
su vida Todo todo Claro si para ella es
private and you can't comment on the
privado y no se puede comentar los
spaces imag
espacios imag
if they base themselves on something public to say
si se basan en algo público para decir
that she works in a hotel it's that
que trabaje en un hotel es que más
even more private you can't
privado todavía no se puede
say I It's that I just don't understand
decir yo Es que es que no entiendo De
where these ladies got that
dónde se han sacado estas señoras que
Twitter spaces  They are private if
los espacios de Twitter son privados si
you want Have a private conversation
tú quieres Ten una conversación privada
chick you open
pava te abres
one you open a deard session or whatever
una abres una sesión deard o lo que sea
and you talk and and criticize whoever you want
y habláis y y criis a qui os de la gana
at the moment you are doing it
en el momento en que lo estás haciendo
on Twitter openly it is not private
en Twitter en abierto no es privado
and you can comment on everything you say
y se puede comentar todo lo que digáis
in that space no matter how you
en ese space te pongas como te
feel no they hide behind that
pongas no ell se escudan en eso que
they are private people they can
ellas son gente privada ellas pueden
insult rant but also with
insultar despotricar pero también con
but that goes for Antonio David also
pero eso va para Antonio David también
Antonio as if it were private his also you
Antonio como si fuera privado también de
cannot comment even if he is a
él no se puede comentar aunque sea
youtuber but for the rest as we are as we
youtuber pero del resto como somos como
appear on YouTube Yes I have made sure that what
salimos en YouTube Sí yo me he asegurado
I have said is not illegal
que esto que he dicho no es ilegal
Because if it were illegal I would have sent
Porque si fuera ilegal hubiera mandado a
FJ to do it
FJ hacerlo
because yes as
porque sí como
always terrible to me what makes me
siempre terrible a mí lo que me hace
laugh sipre and I and I go up to your channel to
gracia sipre y yo y yo subo a tu canal a
give you the rounds and make you cry that They
echarte la ronda y hacerte llorar que
still continue with that refrain and he
Todavía siguen con la cantinela esa y me
passes me the outline of the videos of the
pasa la escaleta de los vídeos de los
live of everything It makes me laugh that they
directos de todo A mí me hace gracia que
expect from before a viid that she will
esperen de ante una viid que se
position herself in favor of Tania when Anton
posicione a favor de Tania cuando anton
Avid does not give the  face for no one
avid no da la cara por nadie
loves let's see I no longer believe that nothing
ame a ver yo ya no no creo que nada
has limits in this life and in everything
tenga límite en esta vida y en todo lo
that surrounds us and each new thing that we see
que nos rodea y cada cosa que vemos
in each post the internet that helps you
nueva en cada pón internet que le ayude
Tania you imagine Antonio David
Tania tú imagínate Antonio David
taking a position on this and say a kiss
posicionándose en esto y decir un beso
Tania we are talking about a sentence of child
Tania estamos hablando una sentencia de
abuse to a minor since the
abuso a menores a una menor desde los 10
age of 10 and a sentence of
años y una sentencia de violencia de
gender violence which is because it is a sentence
género que es porque es una sentencia la
people relate there is gender violence
gente relacion hay violencia de género
also I don't know people talk about the people
también no s la gente habla del la gente
talk about pedophilia the child
habla de lo de la pederastia lo de la
abuse I don't know I don't know how much but
abuso a menores no sé no sé cuánto pero
the sentence condemns for
es que en la sentencia condena por abuso
child abuse for a few years and for
a menores unos cuantos de años y por
gender violence for mistreatment eh be
violencia de género por maltrato eh sea
imagine t vi coming out of t a kiss
imagínate t vi saliendo deí t un beso
that we are already it is that he is going to open his mouth and
que ya vamos es que va a abrir la boca y
the bread is going to rise because
va a subir el pan porque no va a estar
the greatest of the things that love is not going to be there I mean
la mayor de las cosio que el amor O sea
read for Antonio David because why do
que lea por Antonio David porque por qué
they want Antonio David to get involved in
quieren que Antonio David se meta en
this mess they do not protect him at all because of
este jaleo no le protegen nada porque
course they want to see him involved in all this
claro quieren verle metido en todo este
mess if the pras would protect him  and they would say
tingl si la pras le protegerían y dirían
Antonio David not to get into this mess
Antonio David que no se metan estos líos
that it will bring him problems and that
que le va a traer problemas y que vaya
his thing goes, they do not want them to get into this
lo suyo no quieren que se metan este
mess just because of the hatred they have for
jaleo solo por el odio que te tienen a
you, or rather, greater than the hatred they have for
ti o sea superior el odio que tienen a
you Antonio David when no, no, the
ti Antonio David cuando no no a la
truth is, Anio David, no, he does not say anything
verdad anio David no no dice nada
about Claro issues, that is, I know that he did not
de temas de claro o sea se yail que no
mention that he is going to get into this mess so that it
mencionó se va a meter en este jaleo
affects him and for him to be
para que le salpique a él y estar el
involved in the middle is that he would be stupid and
metido por medio es que sería de tonto y
apart from that, it is an issue that neither
aparte que es que es un tema que a él ni
goes nor comes to him. Of course, but They
le va ni le viene Claro pero Ellas
want him to get into the mess, of
quieren que se meta él en el fregado
course, to give his opinion or to support
claro opinar o a apoyar a
Tania, he has to give wax, he has [ __ ],
Tania tiene para dar cera tiene a [__]
really, with the content, if he makes the
en verdad con el contenido si hace el
change, it will be easy for him, but he is not going to
cambio lo tiene fácil pero no lo va a
do it, he is in another but p, he is not going to take it, he is
hacer está en otro pero p no va a [__]
going to come out and tell her a kiss, stop, he has not
va a salir a decirle t beso para no ha
said anything about this either, it is that in
dicho nada de esto tampoco es que en la
truth those who have said a kiss have already
verdad los que han dicho un beso ya se
gone crazy, but it is that, I mean, yes,
le ha ido la la la olla pero es que o
yes, we are sincere, eh, I think, I think,
sea si si somos sinceros eh yo creo creo
eh, that maybe it is my perception and
eh que a lo mejor es percepción mía y
tomorrow  I'm surprised and I say now and I get off the
mañana me sorprende y digo ya y me bajo
world but I think she learned her
del mundo pero yo creo que aprendió la
lesson at the time when she was sending
lección en su momento cuando le mandaba
kisses to Loli while Loli was already causing
besos a Loli mientras Loli ya la estaba
trouble, I mean when when I mean she had
liando o sea cuando cuando o sea todavía
n't yet caused trouble like Loli did
no había liado la de Dios como la Lio
later but she was already, Eh, she had already
después pero ya estaba Eh ya había
called, eh, she mistreats such and such from the flight and and
llamado eh maltrata tal del el vuelo y y
so on and she went out to give her a kiss and and
demás y ya salió a darle un beso y y
we're like family and I don't know what and I don't know
somos como familia y no sé qué y no sé
how many and I think she already learned her
cuántos y yo creo que ella ya aprendió
lesson and she said I'm going to send her Rita you
la lección Y dijo le voy a mandar Rita
know ad
sabes ad